Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers, 1931-2014 MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Non-commercially Released Media, 267152
  - Subseries B: Video recordings, 269261
    - "Annie + 7 Chakras" Linda Montano, February 12, 1989; ID: 386.0180; 270718 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0180)
      "OSU '84. SUB - Master. Linda Montano's: Annie Sprinkle Art in Life Performance. Feb. 12, 1989. Katz + Dawgs Gallery: Colorado, Ohio. Camera: Michael A. Lewis"
    - "Annie - AT 200", undated; ID: 386.0181; 270875 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0181)
      "For Linda"
    - "Annie Sprinkle", Fall 1995; ID: 386.0182; 270939 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0182)
      Original format: Video 8mm.
    - "Anorexia", undated; ID: 386.0183; 270851 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0183)
      Originally under Montano's label "Anorexia."
      Original format: U-matic S.
    - "Anorexia: Christine", undated; ID: 386.0184; 270853 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0184)
      "Master"
    - "Anorexia Nervosa", 1981; ID: 386.0185; 270848 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0185)
      Original format: U-matic.
    - "Anorexia Nervosa #2", 1981; ID: 386.0186; 270849 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0186)
      "Five Stories"
    - "Anorexia: Vicki R-1", undated; ID: 386.0187; 270852 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0187)
    - "Archive for Sale", October 8, 2009; ID: 386.0188; 270966 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0188)
      "34 minutes"
    - "Art/Life One Year Performance: Dub 1", undated; ID: 386.0189; 270864 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0189)
    - "Ask One Question: Franklin + Marshall College", September 25, 1990; ID: 386.0190; 270722 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0190)
      "(copy)"
    - "B-roll Beginning with Nose Tricks", undated; ID: 386.0191; 270754 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0191)
      Originally under Montano's label "Beta Videos."
      "Birds, Births, 1xSex"
      Original format: Betacam SP.
    - "Baby Massage" Leslie Day, 1983; ID: 386.0192; 270908 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0192)
      "10 mins"
      Original format: 1/2" open reel.
    - "Bar Alcohol", undated; ID: 386.0193; 270830 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0193)
      Originally under Montano's label "Raw Footage."
    - "Benares", undated; ID: 386.0194; 270766 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0194)
    - "Benares: Edit 2", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0195; 270782 (Box 60, Media ID: 386.0195)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0196; 270819 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0196)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0197; 270820 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0197)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0198; 270821 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0198)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0199; 270822 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0199)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0200; 270823 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0200)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0201; 270824 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0201)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0202; 270825 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0202)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0203; 270826 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0203)
    - "Benares: Edit 2 Final", October 25, 1998; ID: 386.0204; 270827 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0204)
    - "Benares: Edited Version", April 10, 1998; ID: 386.0205; 270767 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0205)
    - "Benares: Edited Version", April 10, 1998; ID: 386.0206; 270769 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0206)
    - "Benares: Edited Version", April 10, 1998; ID: 386.0207; 270816 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0207)
    - "Benares: Edited Version, Revised", September 20, 1998; ID: 386.0208; 270768 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0208)
    - "Benares: Raw Footage", undated; ID: 386.0209; 270756 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0209)
      "Raw Footage transfer from VHS, Super 8 Film transfer. Both Sex Foorage and Accupuncture."
    - "Benares: Test", undated; ID: 386.0210; 270954 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0210)
      "28:30 minutes"
    - "Benares: Trial Edit", September 20, 1998; ID: 386.0211; 270818 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0211)
    - "Benares: Unedited Version", April 10, 1998; ID: 386.0212; 270783 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0212)
    - "Benares: Unedited Version", April 10, 1998; ID: 386.0213; 270817 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0213)
    - "Benares: Unedited Version", undated; ID: 386.0214; 270784 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0214)
      "Two copies"
    - "Benares: Unedited Version", undated; ID: 386.0215; 270828 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0215)
      "Two copies. 1 hr 38 min."
    - "Birth", undated; ID: 386.0216; 270774 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0216)
      "Birth 7x's. T. Carey"
    - "Birth", undated; ID: 386.0217; 270935 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0217)
      "Kids Wave + Miracle of Birth"
    - "Births - 3 views", undated; ID: 386.0218; 270831 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0218)
      "Births - 3 views. Bootleg. 20 mins. 7 min: Home, 7 min: Squat, 6 min: Home."
    - "Bon Voyage, Linda - Mike", undated; ID: 386.0219; 270868 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0219)
      "If you need to make a better dub at source point just let me know."
    - "Breastfeeding", undated; ID: 386.0220; 270832 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0220)
      "Michelle + Joe 2"
    - "Breathing", undated; ID: 386.0221; 270833 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0221)
      "[Kund + Lini]"
    - "Caution: Live Art", May 5, 2001; ID: 386.0222; 270679 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0222)
      "InterMedia"
    - "Chakraphonics", 1996; ID: 386.0223; 270757 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0223)
      Originally under Montano's label "Chakraphonics."
    - "Chakraphonics", 1996; ID: 386.0224; 270758 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0224)
    - "Chakraphonics", 1996; ID: 386.0255; 270785 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0255)
    - "Chakraphonics: Edited Master", June 19, 1996; ID: 386.0477; 271061 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0477)
      Stereo; 32 min.
    - "Chakraphonics: Montano/Fullman", 1997; ID: 386.0226; 270674 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0226)
    - "Chakraphonics: Not Revised", 1996; ID: 386.0227; 270759 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0227)
    - "Chakraphonics: PAL", 1996; ID: 386.0228; 270760 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0228)
      "TRT 32:00. stereo"
    - "Chakraphonics: Revised", May 12, 1997; ID: 386.0229; 270761 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0229)
    - "Chakraphonics: Revised", May 12, 1997; ID: 386.0230; 270762 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0230)
    - "Chakraphonics: Revised", May 12, 1997; ID: 386.0231; 270786 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0231)
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0232; 270763 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0232)
      "45 minutes."
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0233; 270764 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0233)
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0234; 270765 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0234)
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0235; 270787 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0235)
      "45 minutes"
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", 1998; ID: 386.0236; 270950 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0236)
      "46:12, Video Data Bank"
    - "The Chicken Who Learned How To Fly", 1985; ID: 386.0237; 270912 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0237)
      "12 mins. Story: Linda Montano. Music: Pauline Oliveros. Engineer: Brooks Williams. Narrator: Ingrid. Chicken: Mollie. Swan: Tara. Duck: Toby."
    - "Chicken Woman, 1972" Linda Montano, ID: 386.0238; 270678 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0238)
      "segment edit for MADE IN CALIFORNIA"
    - "Chini + Papa + Children", undated; ID: 386.0239; 270891 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0239)
      "12 min"
      Original format: miniDV.
    - "Chini - From Movie", undated; ID: 386.0240; 270893 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0240)
      "Super 8 Dub"
    - "Cinderella" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0241; 270926 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0241)
    - "Coca", April 27, 1990; ID: 386.0242; 270933 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0242)
    - "Dad Art", April 19, 2005; ID: 386.0243; 270706 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0243)
      Originally under the label "Dad Art."
    - "Dad Art", 2005; ID: 386.0244; 270704 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0244)
      Originally under Montano's label "Dad Art."
      "1 Hr 55 Minutes; Linda M. Montano"
    - "Dad Art", 2005; ID: 386.0245; 270705 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0245)
    - "Dad Art", undated; ID: 386.0246; 270709 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0246)
      "2 hrs, 30 min. Linda M."
    - "Dad Art Performance Tape", 2005; ID: 386.0247; 270707 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0247)
    - "Dad Art Performance: with Time Code", 2010; ID: 386.0248; 270961 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0248)
    - "Dad Art Rough: Time Code", April 22, 2005; ID: 386.0249; 270711 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0249)
    - "Dad Art Rough: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0250; 270710 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0250)
      "1 hr, 55 min"
    - "Dad Art: Tape 7", December 26, 2004; ID: 386.0251; 270728 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0251)
      "Tape 7; Last Before 2nd Stroke; Happy Birthday"
    - "Dad Art: Time Code", March 30, 2005; ID: 386.0252; 270708 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0252)
      "2nd correction"
    - "Dad: Canada", undated; ID: 386.0253; 270717 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0253)
      "Eat/Outside; Tape 6"
    - "Dad Document", undated; ID: 386.0254; 270716 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0254)
      "7 Sacraments/Beatitudes; 30 min.!"
    - "Dad Paint", undated; ID: 386.0255; 270703 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0255)
      "Best of Dad Painting - Not in Video"
    - "Dad Part I, Tape 1", 2001-2002; ID: 386.0256; 270694 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0256)
    - "Dad Raw Footage Part II, Tape 2", 2001-2002; ID: 386.0257; 270696 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0257)
    - "Dad Raw #3", undated; ID: 386.0258; 270712 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0258)
      "B-day Cake; start here for end; + caretaker"
    - "The Day After the Night Before", February 5, 1988; ID: 386.0259; 270850 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0259)
      "Starring Myriam Abramowicz, documented by Helene Aylon. Sherry."
    - "Devi Mahatmyam: Ch. 12, 13", March 26, 1988; ID: 386.0260; 270892 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0260)
      "Betsy Ceva, Nadananda"
    - "Dr. Jane Gooding", undated; ID: 386.0261; 270855 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0261)
      Originally under Montano's label "Learning to Talk."
      "Do not rewind. Dr. Jane Gooding T1+2 Original."
    - "Dr. Jane Gooding", undated; ID: 386.0262; 270907 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0262)
      "Start at 90"
    - "Doctor Nurse", undated; ID: 386.0263; 270859 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0263)
    - "Dystonia", October 8, 2009; ID: 386.0264; 270967 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0264)
      "19 minutes"
    - "Dystonia", October 6, 2009; ID: 386.0265; 270974 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0265)
    - "El Chow de Faustine", October 1994; ID: 386.0266; 270720 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0266)
      "Open Studio w/ Linda Montano. 'Lenny Golden'"
    - "Elders", undated; ID: 386.0267; 270802 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0267)
      "Flo Monroe, Holley, Dr. Johnson, Cindy"
    - "Elders Tape 1", undated; ID: 386.0268; 270794 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0268)
      "Elders Tape 1: Tony, Celia, Mom, Dr. Ash, Vera"
    - "Elders Tape 2", undated; ID: 386.0269; 270795 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0269)
      "1 hr."
    - "Elders Tape 3", undated; ID: 386.0270; 270796 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0270)
      "48 minutes. Dr. Johnson, Andy, Seamus, Luba"
    - "Elders Tape 1: With Time Code", 2003; ID: 386.0271; 270800 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0271)
      "Tony, Cecelia, Mom, Dr. Ash, Vera"
    - "Elders Tape 2: With Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0272; 270801 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0272)
      "Irma, Dr. Hull, Agnes, Flo, Holly"
    - "Elders Tape 3: With Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0273; 270803 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0273)
      "Dr. Johnson, Andy, Lights, Luba"
    - "The End Is Near: Edit", undated; ID: 386.0274; 270889 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0274)
      "21:19; color."
    - "Enter - A Fairy Tale: Time Code", July 10, 2011; ID: 386.0275; 270968 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0275)
    - "Facial Expressions for Chakra", undated; ID: 386.0276; 270932 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0276)
      "Netti (Nasal) / Accupuncture / Eyes"
    - "Family + Old People + Sister Rose", undated; ID: 386.0277; 270936 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0277)
    - "Father LeBar", December 10, 2009; ID: 386.0278; 270976 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0278)
      "Next to Last"
    - "Father Lebar: Test", October 7, 2008; ID: 386.0279; 270977 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0279)
      "No Time Code"
    - "Father Lebar: Time Code", November 7, 2006; ID: 386.0280; 270670 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0280)
      Originally under Montano's label "Father Lebar."
    - "A Few Visuals", undated; ID: 386.0281; 270829 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0281)
    - "Five Minute Greeting: Reunion", undated; ID: 386.0282; 270673 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0282)
    - "Flower", undated; ID: 386.0283; 270807 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0283)
      Originally under Montano's label "Manda Barbour; 7 Spiritual Lives of LM"
    - "Flowers", undated; ID: 386.0284; 270797 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0284)
    - "Flowers", undated; ID: 386.0285; 270837 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0285)
      "49.50 min"
    - "Flowers: Linda and Steven", undated; ID: 386.0286; 270772 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0286)
    - "For Elaine, Love Linda as Hilary Clinton", 2004; ID: 386.0287; 270729 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0287)
    - "For Elaine Summers: a Tribute", August 2004; ID: 386.0288; 270713 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0288)
      "Love from: Linda M. Montano; 7 min. tape"
    - "For Linda from Sherlah", undated; ID: 386.0289; 270957 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0289)
      Originally under Montano's label "Student and Fan Work."
    - "Forgiveness Room", undated; ID: 386.0290; 270798 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0290)
      "1 hour"
    - "The Forgiveness Room" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0291; 270681 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0291)
    - "The Forgiveness Room" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0292; 270877 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0292)
    - "French Woman Leading Lullaby: Sonic Meditation", undated; ID: 386.0293; 270929 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0293)
    - "Ganna Montano Talks About His Sister Linda + Father Henry", 2004; ID: 386.0294; 270714 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0294)
    - "Ha! Ha! 'Is That All There Is?'", 2007; ID: 386.0295; 270719 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0295)
      "10 Minutes. A Film by Linda M. Montano."
    - "Handcuff", October 1997; ID: 386.0296; 270752 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0296)
      "Peter Kirby, Media Art Services. Remaster of 1/2" open reel to 3/4" SP. Audio: mixed. trt: 20:08. Tech: JS"
    - "Handcuff with Tom Marioni" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0297; 270675 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0297)
      "20:08; 'Dear Linda - Returning this. Unfortunately, the quality is not good enough to use in show. -Connie'"
    - "Henry Montano Eating and Painting", September 2004; ID: 386.0298; 270693 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0298)
      "Linda Montano, Please Return; Tape 5; Sept. 04"
    - "I Value Your Opinion" Sara Pomerance, 2006; ID: 386.0229; 270955 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0229)
      "4 min."
    - "Icky and Kathy Trilogy" Kathy High, 1999; ID: 386.0300; 270878 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0300)
      "9 minutes"
    - "Irma Sagazie Testimonial", 2003; ID: 386.0301; 270915 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0301)
    - "Irma Sagazie Testimonial", undated; ID: 386.0302; 270778 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0302)
    - "Karate Exam", December 1982; ID: 386.0303; 270745 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0303)
    - "Karate Exam" Linda Montano, December 1982; ID: 386.0304; 270733 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0304)
    - "Kathy High Dad", undated; ID: 386.0305; 270916 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0305)
    - "Learning to Talk", 1976-1977; ID: 386.0306; 270913 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0306)
      "Center for Music Experiment"
    - "Learning to Talk", undated; ID: 386.0307; 270911 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0307)
      "Dub: Curve Phillips"
    - "Learning to Talk", undated; ID: 386.0308; 270928 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0308)
      "A video, characters that I have developed to get over fear of talking."
    - "Learning to Talk: B + W Original", 1977; ID: 386.0309; 270856 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0309)
    - "Learning to Talk: For Master", undated; ID: 386.0310; 270724 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0310)
    - "Learning to Talk, Rope Piece Film Document, Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0311; 270788 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0311)
    - "Leftovers", undated; ID: 386.0312; 270905 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0312)
      Originally under Montano's label "Sex."
    - "Letters from Linda M. Montano", 2005; ID: 386.0313; 270952 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0313)
      "The National Review of Live Art"
    - "Lighten Up: Time Code", 2010; ID: 386.0314; 270963 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0314)
    - "Linda + Tehching Boxing", 1983; ID: 386.0315; 270863 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0315)
    - "Linda as Hilary Clinton with Martha Wilson", June 2000; ID: 386.0316; 270676 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0316)
    - "Linda Chants Chini + Papa with Children", undated; ID: 386.0317; 270941 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0317)
    - "Linda/Les and Annie", undated; ID: 386.0318; 270872 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0318)
    - "Linda M. Montano for Window at New Museum", 1995; ID: 386.0319; 270938 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0319)
    - "Linda Montano", undated; ID: 386.0320; 270910 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0320)
    - "Linda Montano 1 Dad", undated; ID: 386.0321; 270734 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0321)
      "Working Tape 1-5"
    - "Linda Montano 2 Father", undated; ID: 386.0322; 270735 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0322)
    - "Linda Montano 3 Father", undated; ID: 386.0323; 270736 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0323)
    - "Linda Montano 4 Father", undated; ID: 386.0324; 270737 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0324)
    - "Linda Montano 5 Father", undated; ID: 386.0325; 270738 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0325)
    - "Linda Montano 6 Father", undated; ID: 386.0326; 270918 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0326)
    - "Linda Montano 7 Father", undated; ID: 386.0327; 270917 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0327)
    - "Linda Montano 9 Father", undated; ID: 386.0328; 270919 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0328)
    - "Linda Montano at the New Museum", December 6, 1991; ID: 386.0329; 270896 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0329)
      "Tape 1 of 1. Copy"
    - "Linda Montano Father 1: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0330; 270684 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0330)
    - "Linda Montano Father 2: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0331; 270685 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0331)
    - "Linda Montano Father 3: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0332; 270686 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0332)
    - "Linda Montano Father 4: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0333; 270687 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0333)
    - "Linda Montano Father 5", undated; ID: 386.0334; 270688 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0334)
    - "Linda Montano Father 6", undated; ID: 386.0335; 270689 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0335)
      "Maybe last one; Cake B-Day Last"
    - "Linda Montano Father 7", undated; ID: 386.0336; 270690 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0336)
    - "Linda Montano Father 8: Empty", undated; ID: 386.0337; 270691 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0337)
    - "Linda Montano Father 9", undated; ID: 386.0338; 270692 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0338)
      "Paint, Eat, TV, Bed, Diaper, Water Massage Feet/Hands, Linda Walk; Day before stroke; 50:35"
    - "The Linda Montano 'Have You Had a Religious Experience?' Hour", undated; ID: 386.0339; 270925 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0339)
    - "Linda Montano: Indiana State University (copy)", September 30, 1993; ID: 386.0390; 270677 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0390)
    - "Linda Montano Message to the Public", March 1990; ID: 386.0341; 270775 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0341)
    - "Linda Montano: Palm Reading, Performance Teaching, Telephone Tarot, Art/Life Counseling", undated; ID: 386.0342; 270725 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0342)
      "Linda Montano Proposal Description: Tape Sample. In 1976 I made a tape, LEARNING TO TALK. Seven parts of me told success stories, one from each chakra. In 1984 I began 7 YEARS OF LIVING ART and lived each chakra, one a year. In this tape I describe this progression from making a tape (1976), to making myself (1984-91), to making a tape to teach others how to make themselves."
    - "Linda Montano Performance Background", undated; ID: 386.0343; 270742 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0343)
      "Please Note: Thirty Seconds of White Leader: Begin Five Seconds In On First Color (Red). For Linda Montano."
    - "Linda Montano's Family", undated; ID: 386.0344; 270920 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0344)
      "45 min."
    - "Linda Montano's St. Teresa of Avila", undated; ID: 386.0345; 270953 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0345)
      "39 minutes"
    - "Love Sex", May 21, 1997; ID: 386.0346; 270898 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0346)
      "80:00"
    - "Love Sex", May 21, 1997; ID: 386.0347; 270900 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0347)
      "Love Sex - Images on this tape - 1. Nasal with heart over clouds, red around edge - 2. Clouds nice - 3. Put honey in eyes - 4. Clouds - 5. Better eyes "crying" - 6. Sky - 7. Lick fingers - 8. Accupuncture - 9. Sky - 10. Eyes - 11. Dancing birds."
    - "Love Sex" Linda Montano, May 21, 1997; ID: 386.0348; 270789 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0348)
    - "Luba/Forgiveness for Mexico Coop Master", undated; ID: 386.0349; 270721 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0349)
    - "Masks", 2009; ID: 386.0350; 270962 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0350)
      "Glitch 20:40. 1 Hour 4 Minutes."
    - "Matagi: Interview", undated; ID: 386.0351; 270942 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0351)
    - "Matagi Super 8 Movie", undated; ID: 386.0352; 270931 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0352)
      "Walk and Pick Vegetables"
    - "Mehta Document(ary)", undated; ID: 386.0353; 270845 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0353)
      Originally under Montano's label "Two Ayruvedic Doctors."
      "Super VHS"
    - "Mehta Documentary", undated; ID: 386.0354; 270846 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0354)
    - "Mehta Documentary", undated; ID: 386.0355; 270847 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0355)
    - "Mehta Documentary: Dub", undated; ID: 386.0356; 270940 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0356)
    - "Mehtas + Tai Chi", undated; ID: 386.0357; 270937 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0357)
    - "MetamorphoSex" Rose Hansen, undated; ID: 386.0358; 270879 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0358)
    - "Miracle of Birth", undated; ID: 386.0359; 270839 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0359)
    - "Mitchell Payne Slides: Master", undated; ID: 386.0360; 270810 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0360)
      Originally under Montano's label "Mitchell's Death."
      "Mitchell Payne: photos of Mitchell. Photos of photos. Original."
    - "Mitchell's Death", October 1997; ID: 386.0361; 270750 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0361)
      "Peter Kirby, Media Art Services. Remaster of 1/2" open reel to 3/4" SP. Audio: mixed. trt: 22:45. Tech: JS"
    - "Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0302; 270753 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0302)
      "21 minutes. 2 dubs."
    - "Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0363; 270812 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0363)
      "21 minutes. Tape starts at 40 seconds. Ends at 23 minutes, 0 seconds."
    - "Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0364; 270906 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0364)
      "Begin at the Beginning"
    - "Mitchell's Death: A Film by Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0365; 270951 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0365, Case 386.0365)
      "23 minutes"
      Access DVD is available for reading room viewing only.
    - "Mitchell's Death: Art/Life One Year Performance, Fleming Museum", undated; ID: 386.0366; 270809 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0366)
      "21 minutes."
    - "Mitchell's Death: Original", 1977; ID: 386.0367; 270813 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0367)
    - "Mitchell's Death: Original", undated; ID: 386.0368; 270811 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0368)
      Original format: U-matic SP.
    - "Mitchell's Death; Putting on Make Up", 1978; ID: 386.0369; 270814 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0369)
      "Do not use sound. Only image. Put on needles for performance original. U.C.S.D 1978."
    - "Mitchell's Death w/Echo", undated; ID: 386.0370; 270808 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0370)
    - "Mom Art: Time Code", November 1, 2011; ID: 386.0371; 270964 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0371)
    - "Mom Art: Time Code Test", March 7, 2012; ID: 386.0372; 270959 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0372)
    - "Monster Fighter" Leslie Crawford, undated; ID: 386.0373; 270948 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0373)
    - "Montano as Mother Teresa: Time Code", July 8, 2009; ID: 386.0374; 270972 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0374)